<?xml version="1.0"?>
<catalog>  
    <birth>Count the age, not the wrinkles you have. Count the blessings and wonderful experiences you’ve had, not the mistakes you’ve made </birth>
    <birth>Forget the past; look forward to the future, for the best things are yet to come.</birth>
	<birth>Happy Birthday to a person that’s charming, talented and witty, and reminds me a lot of myself.</birth>
	<birth>It’s your birthday and you’re still just as beautiful, genuine and kind as the day I met you. Wishing you a Happy Birthday with gratitude </birth>
	<birth>My birthday wish for you is that you continue to love life and never stop dreaming. May beauty and happiness surround you, not only on your special day, but always</birth>
	<birth>A birthday is a most special day in one’s life. Enjoy yours to its fullest</birth>
	<birth>The advantage of old age is that you get to spread your love to many others</birth>
	<birth>Words alone are not enough to express how happy I am you are celebrating another year of your life! My wish for you on your birthday is that you are, and will always be, happy and healthy! Don’t ever change.</birth>
	<birth>Your birthday is a wonderful occasion all by itself. But for me, it’s a special day allowing me to thank God for all that your friendship has meant to me</birth>
	<birth>You have been there for me no matter what. I love you, my dear friend, and I am so excited to share your special day with you. Your birthday is going to be truly special.</birth>
	<birth>Ever since we were little, you’ve always been there for me. I’m so glad we’re still friends, and I bet that, one day, we’ll be sitting side-by-side in our rocking chairs at the nursing home laughing at all of our crazy times together.</birth>
	<birth>Happy Birthday, my dear friend. I don’t know if I could ever convey to you just how much you mean to me. I can’t imagine where I would be right now without you. You have changed my life for the better.</birth>
	<birth>Having a friend like you has made my life so much easier. You are always there to carry me through my times of trouble. That’s why today, your special day, is a great time to celebrate all that you have done for me.</birth>
	<birth>A friend like you is more priceless than the most beautiful diamond. You are not only strong and wise, but kind and thoughtful as well. Your birthday is the perfect opportunity to show you much I care and how grateful I am to have you in my life.</birth>
	<birth>My dearest friend, today is your birthday, and I look forward all year to celebrating this day with you. I have planned so many wonderful activities and I can’t wait to see your face light up when you see what I have in store for you.</birth>
	<birth>Have a wonderful, happy, healthy birthday now and forever. Happy Birthday!</birth>
	<birth>Because today is a special day, sending birthday wishes simply wouldn’t do, so I’m sending you a day when all of your dreams come true, and a year that means the most to you!</birth>
	<birth>I hope that your special day is full of fun, happiness and everything that you enjoy.</birth>
	<birth>I’m so glad you were born, because you brighten my life and fill it with joy. Wishing you a day filled with love and cheer. Hoping your day will be as special as you are. Happy Birthday!</birth>
	<birth>Your birthday is the first day of another 365-day journey. Be the shining thread in the beautiful tapestry of the world to make this year your best ever. Enjoy the ride!\</birth>
	<birth>Be happy! Today is the day you were brought into this world to be a blessing and inspiration to the people around you! You are a wonderful person. May you be given more birthdays to fulfill all of your dreams.</birth>
	<birth>Because, today is a special day simply sending birthday wishes, wouldn’t do. So I’m sending you a day when all your dreams come true and, a year that means the most to you!</birth>
	<birth>The sun is shining more brightly today as a way to wish you Happy Birthday.</birth>
	<birth>Today, I wish for all of your dreams to come true as you walk on your life path. Count your blessings every day, and realize there are more than years in your life! Celebrate your day!</birth>
	<birth>I wish you all the happiness in the world! :) Bday </birth>
	<birth>Happy birthday!!! wish you all the best from the bottom of my heart.</birth>
	<birth>Here’s to another year of success, health and happiness… :) Bday !!</birth>
	<birth>I hope you have a wonderful Birthday filled with Love and Fun!</birth>
	<birth>Take care always and keep on rocking. :) Bday!</birth>
	<birth>May a happy bright star always light your path. :) Bday!</birth>
	<birth>Just live it out to the fullest and have fun! :) </birth>
	<birth>Age hasn’t spoiled you a bit! I wish you a wonderful birthday.</birth>
	<birth>I hope all your birthday wishes and dreams come true.</birth>
	<birth>I am sending you warm and fuzzy birthday wishes. :) Bday.</birth>
	<birth>Birthday Quotes</birth>
	<birth>It’s the journey that counts not the destination.</birth>
	<birth>It’s the simplest things that make your life count, like a simple wish. Happy Birthday!</birth>
	<birth>It’s your choice, when and how your life’s sparking begins, not age.</birth>
	<birth>Famous Birthday Quotes</birth>
	<birth>Don’t count the years. Count the wishes and all the cheers.</birth>
	<birth>Life is a journey. Enjoy every mile.</birth>
	<birth>Don’t look for a heaven in the sky. Make your own heaven right here.</birth>
	<birth>Birthday Warm Closings</birth>
	<birth>All life’s best to you</birth>
	<birth>All my love</birth>
	<birth>All best always</birth>
	<birth>Best wishes on your birthday</birth>
	<birth>Best wishes</birth>
	<birth>Blessings</birth>
	<birth>Enjoy</birth>
	<birth>God bless</birth>
	<birth>Gratefully</birth>
	<birth>Kind wishes</birth>
	<birth>Happy Birthday!</birth>
	<birth>Hugs and kisses</birth>
	<birth>Lots of love</birth>
	<birth>Love always</birth>
	<birth>Love</birth>
	<birth>Much love to you</birth>
	<birth>Thinking the best for you</birth>
	<birth>Warmest wishes</birth>
	<birth>Warmly</birth>
	<birth>With all best wishes</birth>
	<birth>Wishing you happiness</birth>
	<birth>With love</birth>  
</catalog>